Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Basketball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Men's basketball game videotapes, 1957-2002; Accession 2006-A-029
  - Colgate, 1991 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 170)
  - New Hampshire, 1991 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 171)
  - Lehigh, 1991 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 172)
  - Vermont, 1991 December 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 173)
  - Gonzaga, 1991 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 174)
  - Dartmouth, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 175)
  - Lafayette, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 176)
  - Alumni game, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 177)
  - Hartford, 1991; videotape (VHS) (Box 178)
  - San Diego, 1991, January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 179)
  - Navy, 1992 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 180)
  - CCSU, 1992 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 180)
  - Brooklyn, 1992 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 181)
  - Fairfield, 1992 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 182)
  - Brown, 1992 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 183)
  - Columbia, 1992 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 510)
  - Cornell, 1992 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 184)
  - Dartmouth, 1992 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 185)
  - Harvard, 1992 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 186)
  - Penn, 1992 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 187)
  - Princeton, 1992 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 188)
  - Cornell, 1992 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 189)
  - Columbia, 1992 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 190)
  - Princeton, 1992 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 191)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 191U)
  - Penn, 1992 February 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 193)
  - Harvard, 1992 March 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 194)
  - Dartmouth, 1992 March 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 195)
  - Hungary, 1992 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 196)
  - Vermont, 1992 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 197)
  - CCSU, 1992 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 198)
  - Wagner, 1992 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 198)
  - Lafayette, 1992 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 199)
  - Hofstra, 1992 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 200)
  - Hofstra, 1992 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 201)
  - Connecticut, 1992 December 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 202)
  - Kent St., 1992 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 203)
  - Toledo, 1992 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 204)
  - Colgate, 1993 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 205)
  - Lehigh, 1993 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 206)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 206U)
  - Brown, 1993 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 208)
  - Swarthmore, 1993 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 209)
  - Hofstra, 1993 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 233)
  - Brown, 1993 January 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 210)
  - Columbia, 1993 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 211)
  - Cornell, 1993 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 212)
  - Princeton, 1993 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 213)
  - UPenn, 1993 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 214)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 214U)
  - Harvard, 1993 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 215)
  - Cornell, 1993 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 216)
  - Columbia, 1993 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 217)
  - UNH, 1993 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 218)
  - Harvard, 1993 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 219)
  - UPenn, 1993 March 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 220)
  - Boston College, 1993 April 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 221)
  - Portuguese National Team, 1993 November 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 223)
  - Exhibition, 1993 November 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 224)
  - Boston University, 1993 November 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 224)
  - Colgate, 1993 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 225)
  - Wagner, 1993 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 226)
  - Central Connecticut, 1993 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 226)
  - Connecticut, 1993 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 227)
  - LaSalle, 1993 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 228)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 228U)
  - Sam Houston, 1993 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 230)
  - Holy Cross, 1993 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 231)
  - UConn, 1993 December 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 231)
  - UNH, 1993 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 232)
    - Duplicating master, 6
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 232U)
  - Hartford, 1993 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 233)
  - Hofstra, 1993 December 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 234)
  - Kent State, 1993 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 235)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 235U)
  - Cincinnati, 1993 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 237)
  - Indiana, 1994 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 237)
  - Dartmouth, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 238)
  - Vermont, 1994 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 239)
  - Xavier, 1994 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 240)
  - Lehigh, 1994 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 240)
  - Lafayette, 1994 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 241)
  - Lehigh, 1994 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 242)
  - Bucknell, 1994 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 243)
  - Fairfield, 1994 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 243)
  - Swarthmore, 1994 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 244)
  - Brown, 1994 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 245)
  - Brown, 1994 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 247)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 247UA)
  - Cornell, 1994 January 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 248)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 248UA)
  - Columbia, 1994 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 250)
  - Harvard, 1994 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 252)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 252UA)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 253)
  - Penn, 1994 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 254)
  - Princeton, 1994 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 255)
  - Columbia, 1994 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 256)
  - Cornell, 1994 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 248)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 248UB)
  - Pennsylvania, 1994 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 258)
  - Princeton, 1994 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 259)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 260)
  - Harvard, 1994 March 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 252)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 252UB)
  - Brown, 1994 March 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 247)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 247UB)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 October 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 264)
  - Cornell, 1994 November 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 265)
  - Slokavia, 1994 November 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 266)
  - Slovakia, 1994 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 267)
  - Maine, 1994 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 268)
  - Georgia St., 1994 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 269)
  - Lehigh, 1994 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 270)
  - UConn, 1994 December 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 271)
    - Duplicating master, 7
    - Use copy, 1; and 1 optical disc (DVD) (Box 271U1–271U2)
  - St. Michaels, 1994 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 273)
  - Seton Hall, 1994 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 274)
  - Army, 1994 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 275)
  - Lafayette, 1994 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 276)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 276U)
  - Eastern Michigan, 1994 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 278)
  - Alcorn State, 1994 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 279)
  - USD, 1995 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 280)
  - Murry St., 1995 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 281)
  - New Hampshire, 1995 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 281)
  - Brown, 1995 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 282)
  - Hartford, 1995 January 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 283)
  - Army, 1995 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 284)
  - St. Francis, 1995 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 285)
  - Fairfield, 1995 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 286)
  - Swarthmore, 1995 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 287)
  - Hofstra, 1995 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 288)
  - Brown, 1995 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 289)
  - Brown, 1995 January 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 290)
  - Brown, 1995 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 291)
  - Cornell, 1995 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 292)
    - Duplicating master, 7
    - Use copy, 1; and 1 optical disc (DVD) (Box 292U1–292U2)
  - Columbia, 1995 January 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 294)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 294U)
  - St. Francis, 1995 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 296)
  - Princeton, 1995 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 297)
  - Penn, 1995 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 298)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 298U)
  - Princeton, 1995 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 300)
    - Duplicating master, 7
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 300U)
  - Dartmouth, 1995 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 301)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 301U)
  - Harvard, 1995 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 304)
    - Duplicating master, 8
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 304U)
  - Harvard, 1995 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 305)
    - Duplicating master, 10
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 305U)
  - Columbia, 1995 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 306)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 306U)
  - Cornell, 1995 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 308)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 308U)
  - Lehigh, 1995 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 310)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 310U)
  - Harvard, 1995 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 312)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 312U)
  - Dartmouth, 1995 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 314)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 314U)
  - Penn, 1995 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 316)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 316U)
  - Chad Slovick Highlight, 1995 April 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 318)
  - Delaware, 1995 September; videotape (VHS) (Box 319)
  - Ukraine, 1995 November 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 320)
  - Rice, 1995 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 321)
  - Stetson, 1995 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 322)
  - Lehigh, 1995 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 323)
  - Swarthmore, 1995 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 324)
  - Holy Cross, 1995 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 325)
  - UConn, 1995 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 326)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 326U)
  - Army, 1995 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 328)
  - Long Island, 1995 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 329)
  - Georgia Southern, 1995 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 330)
  - Colgate, 1996 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 331)
  - Penn, 1996 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 332)
  - Brown, 1996 January 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 333)
  - Brown, 1996 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 334)
  - St. Thomas Moore, 1996 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 335)
  - Harvard, 1996 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 336)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 336U)
  - Dartmouth, 1996 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 338)
  - Army, 1996 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 339)
  - Cornell, 1996 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 340)
  - Columbia, 1996 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 341)
  - Lafayette, 1996 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 342)
  - Penn, 1996 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 343)
  - Columbia, 1996 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 344)
  - Cornell, 1996 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 345)
  - Dartmouth, 1996 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 346)
    - Duplicating master, 10
    - Use copies, 1; and 1 optical disc (DVD) (Box 346U1–346U2)
  - Harvard, 1996 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 348)
    - Duplicating master, 7
    - Use copy, 1; and 1 optical disk (DVD) (Box 348U1–348U2)
  - Diamonds, 1996 November 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 350)
  - Hartford, 1996 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 351)
  - Holy Cross, 1996 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 352)
  - Swarthmore, 1996 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 353)
  - Lehigh, 1996 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 354)
  - Charleston Southern, 1996 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 355)
  - Lafayette, 1996 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 356)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 356U)
  - Army, 1996 December 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 358)
  - SMU, 1997 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 359)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 359U)
  - Penn, 1997 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 361)
  - Princeton, 1997 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 362)
  - Lafayette, 1997 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 363)
  - Brown, 1997 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 364)
  - Siena, 1997 January 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 365)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 365U)
  - Brown, 1997 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 367)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 368)
  - Harvard, 1997 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 369)
  - Columbia, 1997 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 370)
  - Cornell, 1997 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 371)
  - Penn, 1997 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 372)
  - Columbia, 1997 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 373)
  - Harvard, 1997 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 374)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 375)
  - Lehigh, 1997 November 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 376)
  - Holy Cross, 1997 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 377)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 377U)
  - Siena, 1997 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 379)
  - Fairfield, 1997 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 479)
  - Central Connecticut State, 1997 December 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 380)
  - Army, 1997 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 381)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 381U)
  - Drake University, 1997 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 383)
  - New Mexico, 1997 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 384)
  - Penn, 1997; videotape (VHS) (Box 484)
  - Swarthmore, 1998 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 385)
  - Princeton, 1998 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 386)
  - St. Francis, 1998 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 387)
  - Brown, 1998 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 388)
  - Brown, 1998 January 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 389)
  - Dartmouth, 1998 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 390)
  - Harvard, 1998 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 391)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 391U)
  - Columbia, 1998 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 393)
  - Cornell, 1998 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 394)
  - Penn, 1998 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 395)
  - Princeton, 1998 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 396)
  - Dartmouth, 1998 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 397)
  - Cornell, 1998 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 398)
  - Columbia, 1998 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 399)
  - Harvard, 1998 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 400)
  - Dartmouth, 1998 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 401)
  - Holy Cross, 1998 November 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 402)
  - Notre Dame, 1998 November 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 403)
  - New Hampshire, 1998 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 404)
  - Fordham, 1998 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 405)
  - Penn, 1999 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 406)
  - Princeton, 1999 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 407)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 407U)
  - Brown, 1999 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 408)
  - Swarthmore, 1999 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 409)
  - Brown, 1999 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 410)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 410U)
  - Harvard, 1999 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 412)
  - Dartmouth, 1999 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 413)
  - Cornell, 1999 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 414)
  - Princeton, 1999 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 415)
  - Penn, 1999 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 416)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 416U)
  - Columbia, 1999 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 417)
  - Harvard, 1999 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 418)
  - Blue/White Scrimmage, 1999 November 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 419)
  - Converse All Stars, 1999 November 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 420)
  - Lehigh, 1999 November 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 421)
  - University of Colorado, 1999 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 422)
  - University of Denver, 1999 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 423)
  - Central Connecticut, 1999 December 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 424)
  - Quinnipiac, 1999 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 425)
  - Army, 1999 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 426)
  - Holy Cross, 1999 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 427)
  - St. Francis, 1999 December 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 428)
  - NCSU, 1999 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 429)
  - High Point University, 1999 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 430)
  - Liberty University, 2000 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 431)
  - Harvard, 2000 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 432)
  - Dartmouth, 2000 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 433)
  - Brown, 2000 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 434)
  - University of Albany, 2000 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 435)
  - Penn, 2000 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 436)
  - Penn, 2000 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 437)
  - Princeton, 2000 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 438)
  - Cornell, 2000 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 439)
  - Columbia, 2000 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 440)
  - Dartmouth, 2000 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 441)
  - Harvard, 2000 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 442)
  - Columbia, 2000 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 443)
  - Cornell, 2000 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 444)
  - Princeton, 2000 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 445)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 445U)
  - UMass-Lowell, 2000 November 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 447)
  - Ohio State, 2000 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 448)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 448U)
  - Cleveland State, 2000 November 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 450)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 450U)
  - Long Island, 2000 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 452)
  - Colorado State, 2000 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 453)
  - Colgate, 2000 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 454)
  - Rhode Island, 2000 December 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 455)
  - Cal, 2000 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 456)
  - Blue/White, 2000; videotape (VHS) (Box 457)
  - Season Highlights, 2000-2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 481)
  - Army, 2001 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 485)
  - Holy Cross, 2001 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 486)
  - Dartmouth, 2001 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 487)
  - Brown, 2001 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 488)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 488U)
  - Penn State, 2001 January 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 489)
  - Penn, 2001 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 490)
  - Columbia, 2001 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 491)
  - Harvard, 2001 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 492)
  - Columbia, 2001 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 493)
  - Cornell, 2001 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 494)
  - Princeton, 2001 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 495)
  - Pennsylvania, 2001 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 496)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 496U)
  - Brown, 2001 March 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 497)
  - Air Force (Guardians Classic in Columbia, MO), 2001 November 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 498)
  - Tennessee-Martin (Guardians Classic in Columbia, MO), 2001 November 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 511)
  - Stony Brook (Guardians Classic in Columbia, MO), 2001 November 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 499)
  - George Washington (Red Auerbach Colonial Classic in Washington, DC), 2001 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 500)
  - Sacred Heart, 2001 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 501)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 501U)
  - Army, 2001 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 502)
  - Colgate, 2001 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 503)
  - Long Island, 2001 December 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 504)
  - Albany, 2001 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 505)
  - Gardner (Poinsettia Holiday Classic in Greenville, SC), 2001 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 506)
  - Tennessee Tech, 2002 March 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 458)
  - Aubrey West, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 459)
  - BU, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 460)
  - Brown, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 461)
  - SCSU, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 462)
  - Fairfield, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 463)
  - Hartford, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 464)
  - Hofstra, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 465)
  - New Hampshire, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 466)
  - Rutgers, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 467)
  - San Diego State, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 468)
  - St. Francis, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 469)
  - Princeton plus news clips, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 470)
  - UConn, undated; videotape (U-matic) (Box 480)
  - NIT coverage, commercially-produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 482)
  - WMGC-TV [commercially-produced], undated; 1 (Box 483)
  - Lehigh, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 513)
  - UCF (end of 4th quarter), undated; 1 (Box 478)
- Women's basketball game videotapes, 1985-2003; Accession 2006-A-030
  General
  There is no box 20 in this accession.
  - Brown, 1985 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Penn, 1985 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 2U2)
  - Princeton, 1985 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 2U1)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 2U2)
  - Brown, 1986 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Harvard, 1986 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Harvard, 1986 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Penn, 1986 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 6Ub)
  - Penn, 1986 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Brown, 1987 January 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Brown, 1987 January 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Princeton, 1987 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Penn, 1987 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 8U)
  - Princeton, 1987 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Dartmouth, VHS videotap, 1987 February 6 (Box 10)
  - Harvard, 1987 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Harvard, 1987 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Dartmouth, 1987 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Penn, 1987 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 8U)
  - Penn, 1988 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 12)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 12U)
  - Harvard, 1988 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Columbia, 1988 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Penn, 1988 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 12)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 12U)
  - Harvard, 1988 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 15)
  - Hartford, 1988 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Iowa State, 1988 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Brown, 1989 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Army, 1989 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Brown, 1989 January 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Penn, 1989 January 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 21U)
  - Princeton, 1989 January 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Cornell, 1989 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Columbia, 1989 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Harvard, 1989 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Dartmouth, 1989 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Princeton, 1989 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 22UB)
  - Penn, 1989 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 21U)
  - Dartmouth, 1989 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Harvard, 1989 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Columbia, 1989 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Cornell, 1989 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Navy, 1989 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 28)
  - Fairfield, 1990 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 29)
  - Lafayette, 1990 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 30)
  - Lehigh, 1990 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 31)
  - Penn, 1990 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 32)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 32U)
  - Brown, 1990 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 33)
  - Army, 1990 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 34)
  - Cornell, 1990 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 35)
  - Columbia, 1990 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 36)
  - Penn, 1990 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 32)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 32U)
  - Columbia, 1990 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 36)
  - Cornell, 1990 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 35)
  - Army, 1990 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 37)
  - Iona, 1990 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 38)
  - Brooklyn, 1990 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)